Again, I close this tab, and I come to the home page, and I come to create with AI.
And after images, we also have, let's say, posters, banners, invitations, social posts.
These are all the same, right?
So we go ahead with posters, but the exact same steps that we take to create a poster,
that's pretty much the same with social posts, with banners, et cetera, right?
So I click on posters, and we will be able to, will be forwarded to the design creator,
as you see over here.
So for example, if I also say invitation, it refers me to invitations.
So if I say banners, it refers me to banners, you know?
But the point here is that the process is very similar.
So again, there's a prompt, you know?
And there's sometimes an image, but sometimes not.
So for example, in this banner thing, as you see, it only wants me to describe my banner
and specify the size.
And that's all.
But when it comes to posters, it wants me to add a description and also give it an image
if I want to, you know?
When it comes to invitation, it first wants me to choose one of these available templates,
right?
And I can edit each prompt.
So as you see, there are small differences between them, but at the end, it's an AI tool,
you know?
Nothing changes that much.
But for example, as you see, if I click on social posts, or if I click on posters, both
of them will lead me to the design creator tool, you know?
But this time, it's a design creator for post, but this time is the design creator for posters,
you know?
But the tool is similar, as you see.